A Guide to the Richmond (Va.), Bureau of Permits and Inspections, Building permit architectural blueprints and specifications, 1907-1976
Library of Virginia
- Blueprint drawings, 1907-1950, 3167 sets of blueprints
  - Factories, 1908-1948, undated
    - Factory - Permit Number: N/A, Wholesale Market, Swift & Co., Address: N/A, 1923 (Folder 98)
      Drawn by: Construction Dept. Chicago; Contractor: N/A; Commissioned by: Swift & Company, Richmond, Virginia; Notes: Plans showing original building (1909; see Control #97) and addition (1918). It is unclear as to the purpose of these plans. They may have been submitted for the addition dated 1918. Sheets from Control #97 plans were mixed with these and have been placed in the proper location.
    - Factory - Permit Number: 12370A, Addition to Building for Southern Stove Works, Address: 4th and Morgan Sts., 1923 (Folder 785)
      Drawn by: Unsigned; Contractor: J. T. Nuckols; Commissioned by: Southern Stove Works; Notes: Steel, reinforced concrete addition to existing brick warehouse.
    - Factory - Permit Number: 11380, National Biscuit Company, Address: 1320 N. Boulevard, 1923 (Folder 548)
      Drawn by: Davis Bros., Inc.; Contractor: Davis Bros., Inc; Commissioned by: Davis Bros., Inc.; Notes: One-story over raised basement brick factory / manufacturing building.
    - Factory - Permit Number: 15284, Factory Building for Mr. H. H. Nolte, Address: 413 E. Canal St., 1924 (Folder 654)
      Drawn by: W. T. Davis; Contractor: J. T. Nuckols; Commissioned by: H. H. Nolte; Notes: Four story brick and stucco factory building.
    - Factory - Permit Number: 13232, Warehouse and Factory Building for the Wortendyke Mfg. Co., Address: 13th and Byrd Sts., Richmond, 1924 (Folder 610)
      Drawn by: Carneal & Johnston, Architects & Engineers, Richmond, Virginia; Contractor: Harrison Construction Co.; Commissioned by: Wortendyke Mfg. Col; Notes:
    - Factory - Permit Number: 14905, Warehouse for Albemarle Paper Co., Address: Brown's Island, 1925 (Folder 1542)
      Drawn by: Unsigned; Contractor: O. C. Peters; Commissioned by: Albemarle Paper Co.; Notes:
    - Factory - Permit Number: 15912, Residence to be Erected by Muhleman & Kayhoe, Builders, Address: 3619 - 3627 Grove Ave., 1925 (Folder 1213)
      Drawn by: Muhleman & Kayhoe; Contractor: Muhleman and Kayhoe; Commissioned by: W. H. Goodman; Notes:
    - Factory - Permit Number: 14100A, Abattoir & Cold Storage Plant, Address: Southern Air Lines railroad and Hermitage Rd., 1925 (Folder 1373)
      Drawn by: Davis Bros., Architects & Builders, Richmond, Va., Charles K. Bryant, Supervising Architect; Contractor: Davis Bros.; Commissioned by: Joseph Mc Sweeny; Notes:
    - Factory - Permit Number: 13745, Addition to the Albemarle Paper Company, Brown's Island, Address: Brown's Island, 1925 (Folder 1374)
      Drawn by: Unsigned; Contractor: O. C. Peers (?); Commissioned by: Albemarle Paper Co.; Notes:
    - Factory - Permit Number: 14420A, Addition to the Fibre Board Container Co., Address: 3200 Williamsburg Ave., 1925 (Folder 1195)
      Drawn by: James Fox; Contractor: James Fox; Commissioned by: Fibre Board Container Co.; Notes:
    - Factory - Permit Number: 14667, Manchester Power Plant, Address: 10 Decatur St., 1925 (Folder 1462)
      Drawn by: Virginia Railway & Power Co., Engineering Dept.; Contractor: Allen Saville Inc.; Commissioned by: Virginia Railway & Power Co.; Notes:
    - Factory - Permit Number: 14341, Factory for Larus Brothers, Address: 2114 - 2116 - 2118 W. Cary St., 1925 (Folder 1154)
      Drawn by: J. E. Sirrine & Co., Engineers, Greenville, S. C.; Contractor: Wise Granite Contractors; Commissioned by: Larus Brothers; Notes:
    - Factory - Permit Number: 15422, Branch Sales Building 18th & Marshall Sts., for the Wm. Schluderburg T. J. Kurdle Co. Baltimore, Md.. MD., Address: 332 N. 18th St., 1925 (Folder 1386)
      Drawn by: Alfred Cookman Leach, Architect, 411 N. Charles St., Baltimore, Md.; Contractor: Doyle and Russell; Commissioned by: R. H. Stoltz; Notes:
    - Factory - Permit Number: 13929A, Addition to Bakery Building, Address: 2514 - 2516 E. Broad St., 1925 (Folder 1393)
      Drawn by: McCormick Company, Architects & Engineers, Pittsburgh & New York; Contractor: Joseph Fox; Commissioned by: Nolde Brothers Bakery; Notes:
    - Factory - Permit Number: 15466, Plans of Factory Building for Mr. R. A. Bowen-, Address: 206 W. 20th St., 1925 (Folder 1383)
      Drawn by: Courtenay S. Welton, Architect, 701 Grace - American Building, Richmond, Va.; Contractor: E. L. Bass; Commissioned by: R. A. Bowen; Notes:
    - Factory - Permit Number: 13848A, Factory Building, Address: 617 Everett St., 1925 (Folder 1384)
      Drawn by: Unsigned; Contractor: Owner; Commissioned by: Miller Manufacturing Co.; Notes:
    - Factory - Permit Number: 14111A, Fireproof Stair Towers, Address: 25th and Cary Sts., 1925 (Folder 1385)
      Drawn by: L. P. Hartsook, Architect, American Natl. Bk. Bldg., Richmond, Va.; Contractor: E. L. Bass; Commissioned by: American Tobacco Co.; Notes:
    - Factory - Permit Number: 16286A, Hollywood Mill, Albemarle Paper Manufacturing Co., Address: West end of Tredegar St., south of Hollywood Cemetery, 1925 (Folder 1179)
      Drawn by: Carneal & Johnston, Architects & Engineers, Richmond, Virginia, Architects & Engineers, Richmond, Va.; Contractor: Claiborne and Taylor; Commissioned by: Albemarle Paper Co.; Notes:
    - Factory - Permit Number: 15743, Office Building - Cauthorne Paper Co., Address: 209 - 211 - 213 - Hull St., 1925 (Folder 1187)
      Drawn by: Carneal & Johnston, Architects & Engineers, Richmond, Virginia; Contractor: Doyle and Russell; Commissioned by: Cauthorne Paper Co.; Notes:
    - Factory - Permit Number: 14993, Factory for S. Q. Kline, Morgan St., Address: 808 Morgan St., 1925 (Folder 1492)
      Drawn by: L. P. Hartsook, Arch't., American N. B. Bldg., Richmond, Va.; Contractor: E. L. Bass and Bro.; Commissioned by: Industrial Realty Inc.; Notes:
    - Factory - Permit Number: 17003, Horse Shoe Stock House, Address: S. 6th St., 1926 (Folder 1529)
      Drawn by: Tredegar Co.; Contractor: Owner; Commissioned by: Tredegar Co.; Notes:
    - Factory - Permit Number: 17062, 17063, Plans of Factory Buildings for The Virginia Carolina Rubber Co., Inc., Address: 1612 Lewis St., 1926 (Folder 1532)
      Drawn by: Courtenay S. Welton, Architect, 701 Grace American Building, Richmond, Virginia; Contractor: Latham and Taylor; Commissioned by: Virginia Carolina Rubber Co.; Notes:
    - Factory - Permit Number: 17392, Additions to the Milhiser Bag Co., Address: 611-613 Denny St., 1926 (Folder 1122)
      Drawn by: Unsigned; Contractor: N/A; Commissioned by: Milhiser Bag Co.; Notes:
    - Factory - Permit Number: 17326, Coca Cola Bottling Plant, Address: 1805-07 W. Marshall, 1926 (Folder 562)
      Drawn by: O. C. Peers, Contractor and Builder; Contractor: O. C. Peers; Commissioned by: Jas. E. Crass; Notes: One-and two-story brick and stucco plant. Oscar C. Peers was an architect and builder who was active in Richmond from 1911-1922.
    - Factory - Permit Number: 16263, Factory Building for Apex Mfg. Co., Address: 216 S. 5th St., 1926 (Folder 1498)
      Drawn by: Unsigned; Contractor: J. T. Nuckols; Commissioned by: H. H. Nolte; Notes:
    - Factory - Permit Number: 17119, Addition to Richmond Press Building, Governor and Ross Streets, Address: 1314 Ross St., 1926 (Folder 568)
      Drawn by: Unsigned; Contractor: N/A; Commissioned by: G. G. Worsham and C. A. Zincke; Notes: Two-story brick addition to commercial building.
    - Factory - Permit Number: 17425, Awning Manufacturing Plant, Address: 2507 Chamberlayne Ave., 1926 (Folder 1126)
      Drawn by: A. W. Harman, Inc., Builders and Engineers, 15 N. 11th St., Richmond, Va.; Contractor: A. W. Harman, Inc.; Commissioned by: F. E Brown; Notes:
    - Factory - Permit Number: 16319, Alterations & Additions to Factory Building, Everett Waddy Company, Inc., Address: 3-5 South 11th St., 1926 (Folder 1465)
      Drawn by: Carneal & Johnston, Architects & Engineers, Richmond, Virginia; Contractor: Doyle and Russell; Commissioned by: Everett Waddy Co.; Notes:
    - Factory - Permit Number: 16288, Factory Building, Address: 2924 North Ave., 1926 (Folder 1489)
      Drawn by: R. M. Anderson; Contractor: R. M. Anderson; Commissioned by: William M. Morris; Notes:
    - Factory - Permit Number: 15474A, Addition to Plant - Crawford Mfg. Co., Address: 2nd and Decatur Sts., 1927 (Folder 1619)
      Drawn by: Unsigned; Contractor: N/A; Commissioned by: Crawford Manufacturing Co.; Notes:
    - Factory - Permit Number: 18398, Budwine Bottling Co., Address: 1610 Main St., 1927 (Folder 1359)
      Drawn by: Unsigned; Contractor: N/A; Commissioned by: Abraham and Isadore Brown; Notes:
    - Factory - Permit Number: 18171, Bakery for Southern Biscuit Works, Address: 930 North Mulberry St., 1927 (Folder 1621)
      Drawn by: Francisco & Jacobs, Engineers & Architects, New York, Detroit, Chicago; Contractor: Wise Granite Co.; Commissioned by: Southern Biscuit Works; Notes:
    - Factory - Permit Number: 15568A, Alterations to Building at 1363 W. Broad St., Address: 1363 W. Broad St., 1927 (Folder 1682)
      Drawn by: Davis Brothers, Incorporated, General Contractors, L. Otis Spiers, Architect, Richmond, Va.; Contractor: N/A; Commissioned by: Duplex Envelop Co.; Notes:
    - Factory - Permit Number: 18514, Ice Plant for Eugene Robinson, Address: 405 N. 17th St., 1927 (Folder 1356)
      Drawn by: David I. Davis Co., Industrial Engineers, Chicago, Ill.; Contractor: N/A; Commissioned by: Eugene Robinson; Notes:
    - Factory - Permit Number: 17574, Factory Building for Continental Tobacco Co., Address: 1912 - 1918 E. Cary St., 1927 (Folder 1175)
      Drawn by: Francisco & Jacobus, Engineers & Architects, 511 Fifth Ave., New York, NY; Contractor: N/A; Commissioned by: Continental Tobacco Co.; Notes:
    - Factory - Permit Number: 18176, Addition to Cameron Tobacco Company, Address: Railroad Ave. and 9th St., 1927 (Folder 1622)
      Drawn by: Henry T. Barnham, Architect & Engr., Richmond, Va.; Contractor: N/A; Commissioned by: Atlantic Coast Line Railroad; Notes:
    - Factory - Permit Number: 15578A, Addition to Plant for Richmond Dairy Company, Address: 203 W. Marshall St., 1927 (Folder 1689)
      Drawn by: Marcellus E. Wright, Architect, Richmond, Va.; Contractor: N/A; Commissioned by: Richmond Dairy Co.; Notes:
    - Factory - Permit Number: 15586A, Alterations to Building at 1363 W. Broad St., Address: 1363 W. Broad St., 1927 (Folder 1692)
      Drawn by: Davis Bros., Inc., Owners & General Contractors, Richmond, Va., L. Otis Spiers, Architect; Contractor: Davis Bros.; Commissioned by: Duplex Envelope Co.; Notes:
    - Factory - Permit Number: 16285A, Addition to Plant - Crawford Manufacturing Co., Address: 2nd and Decatur Sts., 1928 (Folder 1178)
      Drawn by: Carneal & Johnston, Architects & Engineers, Richmond, Virginia; Contractor: N/A; Commissioned by: Crawford Manufacturing Co.; Notes:
    - Factory - Permit Number: 19252, Laundry Building for Messrs. W. H. Lyne & A. L. Franklin, Address: 1901 Hull St., 1928 (Folder 1654)
      Drawn by: Courtenay S. Welton, Architect, 701 Grace-American Building, Richmond, Virginia; Contractor: N/A; Commissioned by: S & N Laundry; Notes:
    - Factory - Permit Number: 16548A, Sausage Factory - Armour & Co., Address: 307 N. 17th St., 1928 (Folder 1653)
      Drawn by: Unsigned; Contractor: N/A; Commissioned by: Armour & Co. (John Garland Pollard); Notes:
    - Factory - Permit Number: 19067, Printing Plant for Garret & Massie, Inc., Address: 1412 E. Franklin St., 1928 (Folder 1665)
      Drawn by: L. Otis Spiers, Architect, Richmond, Va.; Contractor: Davis Bros. Inc.; Commissioned by: Garret & Massie, Inc.; Notes:
    - Factory - Permit Number: 18664, Factory for Wilson Paper Box Co., Address: 23rd and Franklin Sts., 1928 (Folder 1177)
      Drawn by: Marcellus E. Wright, Architect, Richmond, Va.; Contractor: N/A; Commissioned by: Wilson Paper Box Co.; Notes:
    - Factory - Permit Number: 16288A, Cross-sections & New Addition to Ice Plant, Address: Hermitage Rd., 1928 (Folder 1168)
      Drawn by: Unsigned; Contractor: N/A; Commissioned by: Hermitage Ice & Storage; Notes:
    - Factory - Permit Number: N/A, Factory Building for P. Lorillard Co., Address: Corner 22nd and Cary Sts., 1929 (Folder 1232)
      Drawn by: Francisco & Jacobus, Engineers & Architects, 511 Fifth Ave., New York; Contractor: N/A; Commissioned by: P. Lorillard Co.; Notes:
    - Factory - Permit Number: 17450A, Alterations and Additions for The Simmons Co., Address: 301 Hull St., 1929 (Folder 1786)
      Drawn by: Arthur J. T. Bennett, Engineer & Builder of Industrial Structures, First National Bank Building, Chicago, Ill.; Contractor: N/A; Commissioned by: The Simmons Co.; Notes:
    - Factory - Permit Number: 17580A, Beater and Storage Room for Standard Paper Co., Address: N. side of Canal between Canal and the James River, 1929 (Folder 1776)
      Drawn by: Lee, Smith & Vandervoort, Architects & Engineers, Richmond, Virginia; Contractor: N/A; Commissioned by: Standard Paper Manufacturing Co.; Notes:
    - Factory - Permit Number: N/A, Seventh Street Addition, Ligget & Meyers Tobacco Co., Address: 7th and Canal Sts., 1929 (Folder 1180)
      Drawn by: Francisco & Jacobus, Engineers & Architects, 511 Fifth Ave., New York, NY; Contractor: N/A; Commissioned by: Liggett & Meyers Tobacco Co.; Notes: This building was converted to offices and resurfaced with concrete panels in 1976. It is currently known as the Richmond Plaza Building.
    - Factory - Permit Number: 17387A, Finishing Room for the Standard Paper Co., Address: N. side of Manchester Canal, E. of Hull St., between Canal and the James River, 1929 (Folder 1839)
      Drawn by: Lee, Smith & Vandervoort, Architects & Engineers, Richmond, Va.; Contractor: N/A; Commissioned by: Standard Paper Manufacturing Co.; Notes:
    - Factory - Permit Number: 17544A, Structural Modifications, Address: N/W corner 26th and Cary Sts., 1929 (Folder 1779)
      Drawn by: Francisco & Jacobs, Engineers & Architects, New York - Detroit - Chicago; Contractor: N/A; Commissioned by: American Tobacco Co.; Notes:
    - Factory - Permit Number: 18683A, Alterations and Additions to Bakery Building for Nolde Brothers, Address: 306 N. 26th St., 1930 (Folder 1794)
      Drawn by: The McCormick Co., Inc., Pittsburgh - New York; Contractor: N/A; Commissioned by: Nolde Brothers; Notes:
    - Factory - Permit Number: 20789, Oil Storage Facility, Address: 106 South Maury St., 1930 (Folder 1833)
      Drawn by: Chicago Bridge & Iron Works, Chicago, Illinois; Contractor: N/A; Commissioned by: National Oil Co. (Dominion Oil Co.); Notes:
    - Factory - Permit Number: 20978, Brick Building for Denominational Envelope Co., Inc. Cary & Belvedere Sts., Address: 601 W. Cary St., 1930 (Folder 1757)
      Drawn by: L. Otis Spiers, Architect, Richmond, Va.; Contractor: N/A; Commissioned by: Jefferson Investment Corp.; Notes:
    - Factory - Permit Number: 20818, New Factory Building, American Tobacco Co., Virginia Branch, Address: 2600 - 2618 E. Cary St., 1930 (Folder 1872)
      Drawn by: J. F. Sirrine & Company, Engineers, Greenville, S. C.; Contractor: Wise Granite and Construction Co.; Commissioned by: American Tobacco Co.; Notes:
    - Factory - Permit Number: 18680A, Addition to Building for L. H. Jenkins, Inc., Broad & Allison Streets, Address: 2221 W. Broad St., 1930 (Folder 1797)
      Drawn by: Charles M. Robinson, Architects, Richmond, Virginia; Contractor: N/A; Commissioned by: L. H. Jenkins, Inc.; Notes:
    - Factory - Permit Number: 18316A, Alterations to Roof for Installation of Vapor Extractors, Address: N. side Cary St. between 25th and 26th Sts., 1930 (Folder 1819)
      Drawn by: Lee, Smith & Van Dervoort, Architects & Engineers, Richmond, Virginia; Contractor: N/A; Commissioned by: American Tobacco Company; Notes:
    - Factory - Permit Number: 20824, Steam Power Plant, American Tobacco Company, Virginia Branch, Address: 2624 - 2630 E. Cary St., 1930 (Folder 1836)
      Drawn by: J. E. Sirrine & Company, Engineers, Greenville, S. C.; Contractor: N/A; Commissioned by: American Tobacco Co.; Notes:
    - Factory - Permit Number: 19480A, Addition to Dairy Building, Virginia Dairy Co., Address: 1812 W. Main St., 1931 (Folder 1894)
      Drawn by: Unsigned; Contractor: N/A; Commissioned by: Virginia Dairy Co.; Notes:
    - Factory - Permit Number: 22150, Plan of Addition for The Hopper Paper Co., 8th & Maury Streets, Address: 700 Everett St., 1932 (Folder 1881)
      Drawn by: Unsigned; Contractor: N/A; Commissioned by: Western Tablet and Stationary Co.; Notes:
    - Factory - Permit Number: 20605A, Factory Addition for Milhiser Bag Co., Address: 612 - 618 State St., 1933 (Folder 1898)
    - Factory - Permit Number: 20571A, Alterations and Additions to Building, Harrison & Clay Sts., Address: 1201 W. Clay St., 1933 (Folder 1896)
      Drawn by: Carneal, Johnston & Wright, Architects & Engineers, Richmond, Virginia; Contractor: N/A; Commissioned by: Home Brewing Co.; Notes:
    - Factory - Permit Number: 21486A, Alterations - Richmond Dairy Co., Address: S/S of Marshall St. at Brook Rd., 1934 (Folder 1914)
      Drawn by: Carneal, Johnston & Wright, Architects & Engineers, Richmond, Virginia; Contractor: N/A; Commissioned by: Richmond Dairy Co.; Notes:
    - Factory - Permit Number: 21340A, Alterations to Building for Meat Packing Plant, Rehabilitation Dept., Address: 1235 Hermitage Rd., 1934 (Folder 1946)
      Drawn by: State Headquarters of the Virginia Emergency Relief Administration; Contractor: N/A; Commissioned by: Virginia Rural Rehabilitation Corp.; Notes:
    - Factory - Permit Number: 20935A, Alteration and Addition to Bakery for Nolde Bros., Inc., Address: 320 N. 26th St., 1934 (Folder 1933)
      Drawn by: The McCormick Co., Inc., Pittsburgh - New York; Contractor: James Fox and Sons; Commissioned by: Nolde Bros., Inc.; Notes:
    - Factory - Permit Number: 20715A, Alterations to Plant for Sitterding, Carneal & Davis, Address: 1500 W. Moore St., 1934 (Folder 1936)
      Drawn by: Carneal, Johnston & Wright, Architects & Engineers, Richmond, Virginia; Contractor: N/A; Commissioned by: Sitterding, Carneal & Davis; Notes:
    - Factory - Permit Number: 23262, Factory Building Addition, Address: 24 East 4th St., 1935 (Folder 1926)
      Drawn by: H. Carl Messerschmidt, Architect, Richmond, Virginia; Contractor: N/A; Commissioned by: A. S. Kratz Co.; Notes:
    - Factory - Permit Number: 23217, Three Story Addition to Factory Building, Address: 1915 - 1923 E. Main St., 1935 (Folder 1947)
      Drawn by: H. Carl Messerschmidt, Architect, Richmond, Va.; Contractor: E. L. Bass and Bros.; Commissioned by: Philip Morris Inc.; Notes:
    - Factory - Permit Number: 21919A, Alterations and Additions to Bakery, Address: 10 S. Jefferson St., 1935 (Folder 1915)
      Drawn by: Continental Baking Company, Incorporated, 296 Madison Ave., New York, N. Y.; Contractor: N/A; Commissioned by: Continental Baking Co.; Notes:
    - Factory - Permit Number: 23256, Steel & Concrete Fire Wall for 38,177 bbl Spheroid Tank - Riverfront Property, Address: S/S of James River opposite City Wharf, 1935 (Folder 1950)
      Drawn by: S. E. D., Room 847, 26 Broadway, New York, N. Y.; Contractor: N/A; Commissioned by: Standard Oil Company of New Jersey; Notes:
    - Factory - Permit Number: 23576, Albemarle Paper Mfg. Co., Browns Island Mil, Address: S. end 7th St. on Brown's Island, 1936 (Folder 2591)
      Drawn by: Unsigned; Contractor: N/A; Commissioned by: Albemarle Paper Manufacturing Co.; Notes:
    - Factory - Permit Number: 23695, Factory Building for Baker Equipment Engineering Co., Northwest Corner Summit Ave. and Norfolk St., Address: 1700 Summit Ave., 1936 (Folder 1984)
      Drawn by: H. Carl Messerschmidt, Architect, Richmond, Va.; Contractor: N/A; Commissioned by: Baker Equipment Co.; Notes:
    - Factory - Permit Number: 23618, Virginia Electric and Power Co., 1939 Extension of 12th Street Station No. 2, Address: East Byrd St. between 11th and 12th Sts., 1936 (Folder 1983)
      Drawn by: Stone & Webster Engineering Corp.; Contractor: N/A; Commissioned by: Virginia Electric and Power Co.; Notes:
    - Factory - Permit Number: 23666, Factory Building, Address: 100 - 128 W. 5th St., 1936 (Folder 1970)
      Drawn by: Engineering Department, Reynolds Metal Company, Richmond, Virginia; Contractor: N/A; Commissioned by: Reynolds Metals Co., Inc.; Notes:
    - Factory - Permit Number: N/A, 1936 Extension of 12th Street Power Station No. 2, Address: End of 12th St., 1936 (Folder 1910)
      Drawn by: Stone & Webster Engineering Company, Twelfth and Byrd Streets, Richmond, Virginia; Contractor: N/A; Commissioned by: Virginia Electric and Power Co.; Notes:
    - Factory - Permit Number: 24268, Factory Building, Address: 700 Stockton St., 1937 (Folder 1953)
      Drawn by: Francisco & Jacobus, Engineers & Architects, New York, Chicago; Contractor: N/A; Commissioned by: Philip Morris & Company, Ltd., Inc.; Notes:
    - Factory - Permit Number: 24368, Power House for Philip Morris & Co., Ltd., Address: Rear of 212 East 8th St., 1937 (Folder 2014)
      Drawn by: Francisco & Jacobus, Engineers & Architects, New York and Chicago; Contractor: N/A; Commissioned by: Philip Morris & Co.; Notes:
    - Factory - Permit Number: 23995A, Alterations and Additions to Manchester Board & Paper Co. Plant, Address: N. side of canal, W. of Hull St., 1937 (Folder 2018)
      Drawn by: Slaughter, Saville & Blackburn, Inc., Engineers, Richmond, Virginia; Contractor: N/A; Commissioned by: Manchester Board & Paper Co.; Notes:
    - Factory - Permit Number: 24356, A Bottling Plant for The Subley Beverage Company, 2906 West Broad St., Address: 2906 W. Broad St., 1937 (Folder 2009)
      Drawn by: Unsigned; Contractor: N/A; Commissioned by: William F. Williamson; Notes:
    - Factory - Permit Number: 23978, Building for Crawford Manufacturing Co., Third and Stockton Streets, Address: 300 Decatur St., 1937 (Folder 1992)
      Drawn by: H. Carl Messerschmidt, Architect, Richmond, Virginia; Contractor: N/A; Commissioned by: Crawford Manufacturing Co.; Notes:
    - Factory - Permit Number: 23474A, Additions to Home Brewing Company, Inc., Address: 1125 W. Clay St., 1937 (Folder 1991)
    - Factory - Permit Number: 24941, Superstructure of Office Building for 1939 Extension - 12th St. Power Station, Virginia Electric and Power Company, Address: Byrd St. between 11th and 12th Sts., 1938 (Folder 1278)
      Drawn by: Stone & Webster Engineering Corporation, Boston, Massachusetts; Contractor: N/A; Commissioned by: Virginia Electric and Power Co.; Notes:
    - Factory - Permit Number: 25223A, Underpinning - Present Electrical Bay, Substructure, 1939 Extension - 12th Station No. 2, Address: Byrd St. between 11th and 12th Sts., 1938 (Folder 1345)
      Drawn by: Stone & Webster Engineering Co.; Contractor: N/A; Commissioned by: Virginia Electric and Power Co.; Notes:
    - Factory - Permit Number: 25127A, Building for Crawford Manufacturing Company, Address: 300 Decatur St., 1938 (Folder 2052)
    - Factory - Permit Number: 24503, Ice Cream Factory and Sales Room, 3109 West Broad St., for Arnette Ice Cream Co., Address: 3121 W. Broad St., 1938 (Folder 2024)
      Drawn by: Fred A. Bishop, Architect, Richmond, Virginia; Contractor: N/A; Commissioned by: John F. Sheppard; Notes:
    - Factory - Permit Number: 24582A, Factory Building, Address: 127 W. 6th St., 1938 (Folder 2035)
      Drawn by: International Steel Co., Evansville, Indiana; Contractor: N/A; Commissioned by: Reynolds Metals Co.; Notes:
    - Factory - Permit Number: 25196A, Additions and Alterations to Richmond Piece Dye Works, Address: 301 Hull St., 1938 (Folder 1281)